(Sheldon:)and has been extensively
corroborated
(Sheldon:)by other researchers.
(Penny:)Well, kind of takes the romance
out of relationships.
(Sheldon:)Kind of? It does it perfectly.
(Amy:)Sheldon and I got
(Amy:)an eight-point-two
out of ten.
(Leonard:)Fine. We'll take it
right now.
(Penny:)No, don't.
What?
(Penny:)Just don't take it.
(Leonard:)Why not?
'Cause it's stupid.
(Penny:)Who cares what
number it is?
(Leonard:)Come on. It'll be fun.
I said I don't want you to.
(Penny:)I'm getting
another drink.
(Leonard:)Sorry.
(Amy:)I'm gonna let you
count this as two dates.
(Amy:)They're a lot of work.
(Bernadette:)Think he's getting
any better?
(Raj:)Yup.
WOLOWITZ:
That was a close one!
Okay!
(Raj:)Is it too late
for him to cancel?
(Bernadette:)I think so.
(hollow, metallic bang)